var questionBank=[
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 1,
    question: "What year was the first Fifa World Cup?",
    correctAnswer: 1930,
    incorrectAnswer1: 1946,
    incorrectAnswer2: 1963,
    incorrectAnswer3: 1864
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 2,
    question: "What sport tools do you use in lacrosse?",
    correctAnswer: "A net and ball",
    incorrectAnswer1: "A bat and ball",
    incorrectAnswer2: "A ball",
    incorrectAnswer3: "A stick"
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 3,
    question: "Who's nickname in basketball is Big O?",
    correctAnswer: "Oscar Rober",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Shaquille O'Neal",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Lebron James",
    incorrectAnswer3: "James Hardin"
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 4,
    question: "Who holds the world record for in the mile for 46 days?",
    correctAnswer: "Roger Bannister",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Arnold Palmer",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Venus Williams",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Tim Tebow"
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 5,
    question: "What year was the first March Madness made?",
    correctAnswer: 1939,
    incorrectAnswer1: 1952,
    incorrectAnswer2: 2002,
    incorrectAnswer3: 1986
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 6,
    question: "What NBA player had the most rings?",
    correctAnswer: "Kobe Bryant",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Bill Russel",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Miachel Jordan",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Shaq O'neal"
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 7,
    question: "Who was the first professional baseball team in America?",
    correctAnswer: "Cincinnati Red Stockings",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Atlanta Braves",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Kansas City Royals",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Chicago Cubs"
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 8,
    question: "Who is the best three point shooter in the NBA today?",
    correctAnswer: "Steph Curry",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Lebron James",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Klay Thompson",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Chris Paul"
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 9,
    question: "Who won the three point contest in 2016",
    correctAnswer: "Klay Thompson",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Steph Curry",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Jason Kapono",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Marco Belinelli"
  },
  {
    category: "Sports",
    id: 10,
    question: "When was the first Super Bowl?",
    correctAnswer: "1/15/1967",
    incorrectAnswer1: "2/7/1952",
    incorrectAnswer2: "4/12/1971",
    incorrectAnswer3: "11/5/1948"
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 11,
    question: "What is the capital of Georgia?",
    correctAnswer: "Atlanta",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Nevada",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Virginia",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Maryland"
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 12,
    question: "How many states are in the United States?",
    correctAnswer: 50,
    incorrectAnswer1: 72,
    incorrectAnswer2: 81,
    incorrectAnswer3: 45
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 13,
    question: "How many capitals are in the United States?",
    correctAnswer: 50,
    incorrectAnswer1: 100,
    incorrectAnswer2: 45,
    incorrectAnswer3: 36
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 14,
    question: "What state has Salem for its capital?",
    correctAnswer: "Oregon",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Ohio",
    incorrectAnswer2: "New Jeresy",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Montana"
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 15,
    question: "What is the capital of Washington?",
    correctAnswer: "Olympia",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Hammont",
    incorrectAnswer2: "DC",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Harrisburg"
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 16,
    question: "How many states were in the Conderate Union?",
    correctAnswer: 11,
    incorrectAnswer1: "All 50 states!",
    incorrectAnswer2: 32,
    incorrectAnswer3: 27
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 17,
    question: "What state has Lincoln for its capital?",
    correctAnswer: "Nebraska",
    incorrectAnswer1: "North Corlina",
    incorrectAnswer2: "California",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Pennsylvania"
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 18,
    question: "What is the capital of New York?",
    correctAnswer: "Albany",
    incorrectAnswer1: "New York City",
    incorrectAnswer2: "San Francisco",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Clinton"
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 19,
    question: "What is the capital of Illinois?",
    correctAnswer: "Springfield",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Chicago",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Peoria",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Joliet"
  },
  {
    category: "States & Capitals",
    id: 20,
    question: "What is the capital of Mississippi?",
    correctAnswer: "Jackson",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Delaware",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Kingston",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Tunica"
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 21,
    question: "Which animal is NOT an mammal?",
    correctAnswer: "alligator",
    incorrectAnswer1: "kangaroo",
    incorrectAnswer2: "whale",
    incorrectAnswer3: "bear"
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 22,
    question: "True or False: Platypuses give birth to it's young.",
    correctAnswer: "FALSE",
    incorrectAnswer1: "TRUE",
    incorrectAnswer2: 0,
    incorrectAnswer3: 0
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 23,
    question: "What is the scientific name for bear?",
    correctAnswer: "Ursidae",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Panthera tigris",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Panthera leo",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Aves"
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 24,
    question: "Which answer best decribes the habit of a roadrunner?",
    correctAnswer: "dry and arid",
    incorrectAnswer1: "much rainfall",
    incorrectAnswer2: "freezing snow",
    incorrectAnswer3: "grassy plains"
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 25,
    question: "Which bird can't fly?",
    correctAnswer: "Penguin",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Eagle",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Robin",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Hummingbird"
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 26,
    question: "Which is the biggest species of shark?",
    correctAnswer: "Whale shark",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Great White shark",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Hammerhead shark",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Dolphin"
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 27,
    question: "What is the term for a young horse?",
    correctAnswer: "Foal",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Cygent",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Calf",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Pup"
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 28,
    question: "True or False: Both female and male kangroos have pouches.",
    correctAnswer: "FALSE",
    incorrectAnswer1: "TRUE",
    incorrectAnswer2: 0,
    incorrectAnswer3: 0
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 29,
    question: "Which sea animals DO NOT swim in groups?",
    correctAnswer: "Clams",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Plankton",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Fish",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Seals"
  },
  {
    category: "Animals",
    id: 30,
    question: "True or False: Female praying mantis eat the head of husband.",
    correctAnswer: "TRUE",
    incorrectAnswer1: "FALSE",
    incorrectAnswer2: 0,
    incorrectAnswer3: 0
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 31,
    question: "What is the circumference of a circle with an circle with a diameter of 36?",
    correctAnswer: 113.1,
    incorrectAnswer1: 114,
    incorrectAnswer2: 1017.88,
    incorrectAnswer3: 1017.99
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 32,
    question: "How many sides does a decagon have?",
    correctAnswer: 10,
    incorrectAnswer1: 12,
    incorrectAnswer2: 11,
    incorrectAnswer3: 9
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 33,
    question: "What is the area of a square that has a length of 5?",
    correctAnswer: 20,
    incorrectAnswer1: 25,
    incorrectAnswer2: 15,
    incorrectAnswer3: 30
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 34,
    question: "How many sides does a regular polygon have?",
    correctAnswer: 5,
    incorrectAnswer1: 6,
    incorrectAnswer2: 7,
    incorrectAnswer3: 9
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 35,
    question: "Vertical angles are always?",
    correctAnswer: "Congruent",
    incorrectAnswer1: "90 degrees",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Triangles",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Differrent"
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 36,
    question: "What is the sum of 2 complementary angles?",
    correctAnswer: "90 degrees",
    incorrectAnswer1: "180 degrees",
    incorrectAnswer2: "45 degrees",
    incorrectAnswer3: "360 degrees"
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 37,
    question: "Which side of the triangle is the hypotenuse?",
    correctAnswer: "Longest",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Shortest",
    incorrectAnswer2: "2nd Longest",
    incorrectAnswer3: "None of the Above"
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 38,
    question: "If two lines are intersecting lines they will?",
    correctAnswer: "Touch/Meet",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Never Touch",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Perpendicular",
    incorrectAnswer3: "None of the Above"
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 39,
    question: "Which of the following is not a quadrilateral?",
    correctAnswer: "Triangle",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Rhombus",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Rectangle",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Parallelogram"
  },
  {
    category: "Geometry",
    id: 40,
    question: "How many parallel sides does a parallelogram have?",
    correctAnswer: 1,
    incorrectAnswer1: 2,
    incorrectAnswer2: 0,
    incorrectAnswer3: 3
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 41,
    question: "Who was the author of ‘To Kill a Mockingbird’ ",
    correctAnswer: "Julia Alverez",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Herman Hesse",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Harper Lee",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Barbara Kingsolver"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 42,
    question: "Who was the author of the Harry Potter series?",
    correctAnswer: "J.K Rowling",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Maya Angelou",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Barbara Kingsolver",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Herman Hesse"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 43,
    question: "Who was the author of the Diary of a Wimpy Kid series?",
    correctAnswer: "Jeff Kinney",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Julia Alverez",
    incorrectAnswer2: "J.R.R Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswer3: "John Green"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 44,
    question: "Who is famous for their poetry?",
    correctAnswer: "Maya  Angelou",
    incorrectAnswer1: "John Green",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Barbara Kingsolver",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Julia Alvarez"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 45,
    question: "Who was the author of  The Bean Trees?",
    correctAnswer: "Barbara Kingsolver",
    incorrectAnswer1: "J.R.R Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswer2: "John Green",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Maya Angelou"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 46,
    question: "Who was the author of ‘In the Time of the Butterflies’?",
    correctAnswer: "Harper Lee",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Jeff Kiney",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Julia Alverez",
    incorrectAnswer3: "J.R.R Tolkien"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 47,
    question: "Who was the author of ‘Siddhartha’ ?",
    correctAnswer: "Herman Hesse",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Harper Lee",
    incorrectAnswer2: "John Green",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Suzanne Collins"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 48,
    question: "Who was the author of ‘The Fault in Our Stars’ ",
    correctAnswer: "John Green",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Suzabbe Collins",
    incorrectAnswer2: "J.R.R Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Maya Angelou"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 49,
    question: "Who was the author of",
    correctAnswer: "Suzanne Collins",
    incorrectAnswer1: "John Green",
    incorrectAnswer2: "J.K Rowling",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Harper Lee"
  },
  {
    category: "Authors",
    id: 50,
    question: "Who was the author of the Hunger Game series?",
    correctAnswer: "Herman Hesse",
    incorrectAnswer1: "J.R.R Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Maya Angelou",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Barbara Kingsolver"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 51,
    question: "When was Marvel Comics founded?",
    correctAnswer: 1939,
    incorrectAnswer1: 1801,
    incorrectAnswer2: 1982,
    incorrectAnswer3: 1955
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 52,
    question: "Which superhero owns a golden lasso that can make you tell the truth?",
    correctAnswer: "Wonder Woman",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Supergirl",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Green Lantern",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Beast Boy"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 53,
    question: "Who is Batman's sidekick?",
    correctAnswer: "Robin",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Beast Boy",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Thor",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Flash"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 54,
    question: "What's Peter Parker's middle name",
    correctAnswer: "Benjamin",
    incorrectAnswer1: "William",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Kent",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Sam"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 55,
    question: "What is the Black Widow's real name?",
    correctAnswer: "Natalia Romanova",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Samatha Rogers",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Alicia Perez",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Willma Owens"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 56,
    question: "Complete the name: The Fantasic ______",
    correctAnswer: "Four",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Five",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Sixteen",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Ten"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 57,
    question: "Who is Kal-el?",
    correctAnswer: "Superman",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Batman",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Aquaman",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Thor"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 58,
    question: "What superhero is a part of the Teen Titans?",
    correctAnswer: "Cyborg",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Storm",
    incorrectAnswer2: "The Green Goblin",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Quick Silver"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 59,
    question: "Who has the super strength of something small?",
    correctAnswer: "Antman",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Hulk",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Magneto",
    incorrectAnswer3: "The Thing"
  },
  {
    category: "Comics",
    id: 60,
    question: "True or False: The Joker belongs to DC Universe comics.",
    correctAnswer: "TRUE",
    incorrectAnswer1: "FALSE",
    incorrectAnswer2: 0,
    incorrectAnswer3: 0
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 61,
    question: "What was the date the first episode of Full House aired?",
    correctAnswer: "9/22/1987",
    incorrectAnswer1: "2/12/1982",
    incorrectAnswer2: "5/30/1992",
    incorrectAnswer3: "7/8/1988"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 62,
    question: "What movie featured Jack Black's voice?",
    correctAnswer: "Kung Fu Panda",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Inside Out",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Shrek 2",
    incorrectAnswer3: "How to Train Your Dragon"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 63,
    question: "What was Disney's first animated film?",
    correctAnswer: "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Pinocchio",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Dumbo",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Bambi"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 64,
    question: "What was DreamWorks first animated film?",
    correctAnswer: "The Prince of Egypt",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Chicken Run",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Antz",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Turbo"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 65,
    question: "Who is the creator of Gravity Falls?",
    correctAnswer: "Alex Hirsch",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Rebecca Sugar",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Jeff",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Noah Z. Jones"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 66,
    question: "What was the first show ever created?",
    correctAnswer: "The Man With the Flower in His Mouth",
    incorrectAnswer1: "I Love Lucy",
    incorrectAnswer2: "The Muppet Show",
    incorrectAnswer3: "The Flintstones"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 67,
    question: "Who is the voice actor of Spongebob Squarepants?",
    correctAnswer: "Tom Kenny",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Frank Welker",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Kevin Conroy",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Tara Strong"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 68,
    question: "What was the first movie ever created?",
    correctAnswer: "The Horse in Motion",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Roundhay Garden Scene",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Frozen",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Star Wars"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 69,
    question: "Who is the actress that protrays Buffy the Vampire Slayer in the T.V show?",
    correctAnswer: "Sarah Michelle Gella",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Alyson Hannigan",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Linda Cardellini",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Jennifer Love Hewitt"
  },
  {
    category: "Movies/T.V. Shows",
    id: 70,
    question: "Which actress voices Elsa in Disney's Frozen",
    correctAnswer: "Idina Menzel",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Kristen Bell",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Eva Bella",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Rascal Flatts"
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 71,
    question: "How many songs did beethoven write",
    correctAnswer: 100,
    incorrectAnswer1: 32,
    incorrectAnswer2: 17,
    incorrectAnswer3: 38
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 72,
    question: "Who where the lyrcisist that wrote",
    correctAnswer: "Kristen and Robert Lopez",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Daft Punk",
    incorrectAnswer2: "DANC3",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Pentatonix"
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 73,
    question: "How many songs did Mozart write?",
    correctAnswer: 600,
    incorrectAnswer1: 900,
    incorrectAnswer2: 800,
    incorrectAnswer3: 700
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 74,
    question: "What year did hip hop start?",
    correctAnswer: 1999,
    incorrectAnswer1: 1973,
    incorrectAnswer2: 1956,
    incorrectAnswer3: 1969
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 75,
    question: "Who wrote oui?",
    correctAnswer: "Jermiah and Needlz",
    incorrectAnswer1: "nicki minaj",
    incorrectAnswer2: "drake",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Chris Brown"
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 76,
    question: "Who was the first band that simon signed from X factor for his label?",
    correctAnswer: "One Direction",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Fith Harmony",
    incorrectAnswer2: "REM",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Little Mix"
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 77,
    question: "What year did pop start?",
    correctAnswer: 1978,
    incorrectAnswer1: 1970,
    incorrectAnswer2: 1965,
    incorrectAnswer3: 1995
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 78,
    question: "What year did rock start?",
    correctAnswer: "1950s",
    incorrectAnswer1: "1930s",
    incorrectAnswer2: "1960s",
    incorrectAnswer3: "1970s"
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 79,
    question: "What year did country start?",
    correctAnswer: "1700s",
    incorrectAnswer1: "1600s",
    incorrectAnswer2: "1800s",
    incorrectAnswer3: "1500s"
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: 80,
    question: "Who was the start of alternative music?",
    correctAnswer: "REM",
    incorrectAnswer1: "Nirvana",
    incorrectAnswer2: "Demi Lavato",
    incorrectAnswer3: "Jordin Sparks"
  }
]
